caraca hand
what a fucking club
Instagram is also old fire
look at this
Oh
Get
It on
oh to do an event it's not just putting on a chair
I also had to do the management
financial
control of who paid
who didn't pay
theory i thought right bro
I'll get a paper
a pen
write down the list of people
then due to the rain there were people who did not come
there were people who sent another Person somewhere
in a mess
but then I realized that I was losing myself for nothing Cara
because it's just me getting here at my bank
and open
oh here I put management
check all slips
and here are the names of the people
and how much they paid bro
I won't pass on everyone's name here
and then instead of spending paper and pen
it's much easier for me to have this control
I want to see if it's rascal
Give It Up
now I cleaned it all up
go do what has to end
Juninho
still good
does nothing at all
so far only I clean this shed here
I got a notification from Instagram
I was really upset man
look at this
if you didn't understand
basically
he means his reels are over 3 minutes old
he doesn't recommend it for new audiences guy
how do i put the end of the day
and until tomorrow if he recommends
but I will try to quickly explain the decision to you
that I took
good is the following
it's bag bro time
Baby Lord